{
  "title": "Idioms with the phrasal verb get",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "After the small talk was over, it was time for the two heads of state to ........ discussions concerning bilateral relations between the two countries.  ",
      "answers": [
        "get through with",
        "get by with",
        "get down to",
        "get around"
      ],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "My accountant advised me that one of the best ways to ........ paying taxes in my own country was to set up an offshore bank account. ",
      "answers": ["get away with", "get by with", "get down to", "get around"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": " The high school teacher was so strict that he would not let his students ........ any of the stunts that they tried to pull with their previous teacher. ",
      "answers": ["get away with", "get by with", "get down to", "get around"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Train passengers wishing to go to the football match were advised to ........ the train at the next stop.",
      "answers": ["get on with", "get off", "get in", "get on"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "By the time I ........ you, you will be sorry that you ever stepped foot on the face of this earth. ",
      "answers": [
        "get through with",
        "get by with",
        "get down to",
        "get around"
      ],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The referee instructed both captains to stop their complaining and ........ the rugby matches.",
      "answers": [
        "get by with",
        "get on with",
        "get through with",
        "get by with"
      ],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The days when Americans can ........ in the world on English only will soon be gone. ",
      "answers": ["get in", "get off", "get by", "get on"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Please mind your step when you ........ the train. ",
      "answers": ["get on with", "get by with", "get by", "get on"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "I knew that I had to ......... early the next morning so I set my alarm for 4.30 a.m. ",
      "answers": ["get on", "get off", "get up", "get out"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Employees at the reinsurance company were finding it very difficult to ........ with their new manager.",
      "answers": ["get along", "get away", "get through", "get out"],
      "correct": ""
    }
  ]
}
